mlpforums.com 2015-03-15

# Privacy Policy - MLP Forums

Your privacy is important to us. To better protect your privacy we provide this notice explaining our online information practices and the choices you can make about the way your information is collected and used. To make this notice easy to find, we make it available in our footer and at every point where personally identifiable information may be requested.Log files are maintained and analysed of all requests for files on this website's web servers. Log files do not capture personal information but do capture the user's IP address, which is automatically recognised by our web servers.

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is especially important. For that reason, we never collect or maintain information at our website from those we actually know are under 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract anyone under 13.

**Cookies**  
This website does not store any information that would, on its own, allow us to identify individual users of this service without their permission. Any cookies that may be used by this website are used either solely on a per session basis or to maintain user preferences. Cookies are not shared with any third parties.We also use third-party advertisements to support our services. Some of these advertisers may use technology such as cookies and web beacons when they advertise on our site, which will also send these advertisers (such as Google through the Google AdSense program) information including your IP address, your ISP, the browser you used to visit our site, and in some cases, whether you have Flash installed. This is generally used for geotargeting purposes (showing New York real estate ads to someone in New York, for example) or showing certain ads based on specific sites visited (such as showing cooking ads to someone who frequents cooking sites).

**DoubleClick DART cookies**  
We may also use DART cookies for ad serving through Google’s DoubleClick, which places a cookie on your computer when you are browsing the web and visit a site using DoubleClick advertising (including some Google AdSense advertisements). This cookie is used to serve ads specific to you and your interests (”interest based targeting”).The ads served will be targeted based on your previous browsing history (For example, if you have been viewing sites about visiting Las Vegas, you may see Las Vegas hotel advertisements when viewing a non-related site, such as on a site about hockey). DART uses “non personally identifiable information”. It does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, telephone number, social security numbers, bank account numbers or credit card numbers.You can opt-out of this ad serving on all sites using this advertising by visiting Google's Ad Exchange Privacy Policy page.

**Contacting Us**  
If you have any questions about this privacy policy, Poniverse's practices, or your dealings with us, please contact us at: Poniverse Networks. Or via physical mail:

Poniverse Networks

Suite 2481641 

Lonsdale Avenue 

North Vancouver BC V7M 2J5 Canada

  1. _My Little Pony: Friendship is Magic™_ and all related properties are © Hasbro.
  2.  
  3. [Privacy Policy](http://mlpforums.com/privacypolicy/)
  4. [Global Rules](http://mlpforums.com/index.php?app=forums&module=extras&section=boardrules "Global Rules") ·
